[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'てつだいます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Допомагати"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'てつだい' read in word?",
        "answer": "допомога"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しめます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зачиняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вимикати"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'あけます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відчиняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いそぎます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Спішити"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まちます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Очікувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とまります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зупинятись"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Брати"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まがります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Повертати"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もちます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Тримати"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'つけます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вмикати"
    }
]
